back to this process here could you walk
through kind of visually walk us through
the process of doing a scenario where
you listen you know putting some kind of
mineral in you want to replicate it
beginning to end kind of just step by
step
so and that's only important if you're
actually capturing your hydrogen and
running it I mean you like I said you
have this in a five-gallon bucket but
I'm all about multi-purpose saying I'm
all about finding different ways and so
for boiling hydrogen off you know
there's no purpose to do that unless
we're actually using it and like I said
this is what I'll heat my shop with this
year during the winter we seal it
together we put everything putting or
put everything together we prep our
solution in a gallon or two gallons of
water okay we either use our our high
concentration spring water our saltwater
for brave we use our mineral water
electric water whatever you want to
concentrate you prepare that over here
and you pour that into your reservoir
okay your reservoir which is sitting you
know a high which is marked on the side
to show where you want to where you want
to fill it up to you pour it in there in
the full and the water equalizes and
then you cap your cap your reservoir
just like on my machine over there and
even I take your electrodes you're gonna
take your electricity whether you're
doing it from a generator whether you're
doing it from a solar panel a windmill
generator something like that you're
using a windmill generator I encourage
you to use a battery I'm not a fan of
batteries but with no generators go up
and down and up and down and so you want
a kind of an equalized battery or as
equalized voltage take that power and
you plug it on here positive negative
and you just let it go and just let it
go
if you're collecting your hydrogen you
run it over to your hydrogen collector a
couple of 55-gallon drums
something like that and you just watch
the you just watch the mineral content
as it builds up in your as it builds up
in your reservoir in the reservoir here
it's going to get let's just me it's
going to get darker and darker as the
element content builds up and it looks
like rust it's not rust
like I said we're not disintegrating
plates we've made it the plates and it's
basically the same thing going on in
this main chamber yes as it's going on
in the reservoir that's right because
the two are connected in the way that we
described the two are going to basically
be equal there may be a little bit more
concentration in here that hasn't
traveled over to your reservoir but
that's okay when you say let it go are
you talking hours days room the
concentration that you see here is
probably about 24 hours worth of worth
is running from start to finish with
with clear with a clear additive and the
seed the seed elements 24 hours so
whether that's that was off of a solar
panel so that was about three days worth
maybe four days worth of sunlight okay
if you're running a pure DC source from
a from a generator or something it's
going to be 24 hours and you're gonna
you're going to see a significant
positive there I I don't I haven't felt
impressed to just leave it there okay I
don't want it to short out my plates I
don't want to build up so high I want to
drain it off and and collect it you know
so so did the matter of taking off the
the very simple to do if you have a
reservoir it's even simpler if you have
this configuration because you just undo
that and pour it into a gallon jug if
you have a reservoir you just unhook it
from where you're where you're working
and pour it out and
a gallon jug and then put it back in
place and start again so very simple
very simple way see the video from Tesla
tech my presentation I've got a picture
of it on the wall a very simple system
with the reservoir and the hydrogen
column that are the the bubbling column
there and the flashback arrestor and you
can get a good visual of it oh why do I
keep on forgetting about that it's it
looks just like that very simple just
pour down where you go okay you can oh
you could even have a pigtail off of
here with a little valve that allows you
to open it pour it out and go with that
I always think about those things after
I'm done building but we don't have
Travis what's up how much seed I put
what do you see here
started out I've never added more I
started out with about a bottle of my
electric water and a about three or four
ounces of the gold and platinum okay and
it just keeps on keeps on 3d but for I'd
start out with heck you could even
that's it just makes up a batch of black
sands and put that and pour that in
there of course then you get a lot of
iron oxide we don't want that so never
mind forget I said that
it's an experimental thing we're just
gonna we're going to stir it and see I
mean I'm sure that there are people that
go out and buy colloidal silver for this
thing so remember my lesson that I
mentioned earlier from alchemy silver if
you look in the Bible
silver is current state gold is never
currency silver is currency gold is for
ceremony and enlightenment the silver
medals are far from making money
alchemists are forbidden from using gold
to to make themselves wealthy
Nicholas Flamel made two batches of gold
at like four or five pounds each give it
all away every bit of it build churches
built orphanages build roads
he made silver and kept himself he lived
in the same house as parents gave him
all his life he never went he did travel
and study and learn but he didn't
elevate his status gold to elevate your
status you will get a hammer from the
universe everyone that's trying it has
so platinum platinum is a little bit
different you can sell platinum but here
here's a little here's a little here's a
little secret Platinum is platinum makes
an adamantine lawyer Stanley did not
create the idea of adamantium with you
know Wolverine's skeleton and stuff like
that at a man Adam Ant is referenced in
an eighteen twenties alchemist Masonic
Handbook the referenced it has the
indestructible of Atlantic the
indestructible medal of the Atlantean
alchemists it was made from a composite
of platinum and steel alloys that we
cannot reproduce today they have found
rivets and coffins of these things made
out of this stuff can't even reproduce
it had to be out chemical
so anyway and then they meet back they
may think back to record before recorded
history anyway I mean you know if you're
gasps and you say you put it in
55-gallon drum and you're a specific
gravity that with this gathering you're
bleeding okay my apologies I I have I
have that in my lecture but I had to
skip over that because we were out of
time
it's a 55-gallon drum where the 35
gallon drum inserted into it and you
fill it with with the bottom cut out and
you fill it with water so that as the
hydrogen fills it up it pushes the the
35 gallon drum up and you have grounding
straps in it you have stainless steel
strips inside and out rivet it in place
and then grounding straps out there so
no no no static can build up as you're
doing that's how I store hydrogen and
that way I can use it without
pressurizing it if you pressurize Browns
gas you will die over 100 psi it's at
any point over 100 psi anything explode
I've seen it done up to 60 to inject
into a turbocharger but anything over a
question yeah I'm talking about the
intentions and what about if you're
creating these metals to finance
research and development of clean energy
sources this is a this is a beautiful
and noble purpose the issue what if
you're using the metals that you're
creating to finance research and
development of clean energy sources or
other noble benevolent and that actually
fits with Vulcan le went to the
researchers in France right before World
War two who are trying to build the
atomic bomb and he said what you're
doing
we'll destroy this planet alchemy is the
only answer to stop it that's recorded
in the scientific journals there fokin
le is one of the greatest alchemists of
Europe in the last century but you can
do that and it's akin to it's akin to
Nicolas Flamel using the ghazal chemical
his alchemical metal creations to fund
more of his research into alchemy and
immortality so you can do that the
problem arises when you get people with
egos involved okay a huge amount of
money and research let's say a hundred
thousand dollars is devoted to research
into something and I know this is a
personal experience five thousand
dollars of it goes to the researcher and
a huge amount of money goes to the
administrative costs okay
that's the same thing as profits so you
have to be very careful with the spirit
of the people involved once the spirit
once you get gold involved oh how would
how what is the quote when gold is
involved the laws of God and men are set
at naught now it's Nicholas Flamel when
gold is involved the laws of God and man
are said it not expanding just a little
bit what this means is anybody heard of
gold fever the short term yes the gold
go people know that gold is is the most
important ation of a higher level of
consciousness okay but people that don't
resonate at a higher level of
consciousness see it as something that
they want to obtain at any cost and so
and gold can be considered to be wealth
of gold for these is considered to be
power these are the goal is going to be
the yellow metal and so they desire this
and they will do anything that it takes
to obtain
and control it and so I mean I've seen
people shot not over the gold but over
the the possibility of gold exact so
what you have to do is you have to find
people who will rise above that it's
like I was talking to somebody earlier I
have held an L I've held a rock in my
hand it's a White Rock and it looks like
nothing and if I have a pound of that
and a pound of gold in my hand and an
angel or one of you or somebody came up
and said throw one of them away
I'd throw away the gold in a heartbeat
because the rock is an element that
contains so much power for healing and
energy and health and betterment of the
world but the yellow metal will never be
okay well it could be but but this isn't
its raw form and we can use it so much
better so that's what I do
so when you start dealing with research
and development and bringing and
bringing it making alchemical money for
putting that towards research and
development you have to make certain
that there's nobody scheming of the
coffer there's no egos involved that
it's really the people that are working
on it but absolutely needed that are
getting it or you just start playing
with silver in your okay
and that's only important if you're
actually capturing your hydrogen and
running it I mean you like I said you
could have this in a five-gallon bucket
but I'm all about multi-purpose saying
I'm all about that over here and you
pour that into your reservoir okay your
reservoir which is sitting you know a
high which is marked on the side to show
where you want to where you want to fill
it up to you pour it in there in the
boat and the water equalizes and then
you cap your calculator is a bore just
like back to this process here could you
walk through kind of visually walk us
through the process of doing a scenario
where you listen you know putting some
kind of mineral in and you want to
replicate it beginning to end kind of
just step by step so
to seal up our together we prep our
solution in a gallon or two gallons of
water okay we either use our our high
concentration spring water our saltwater
for brave we use our our mineral water
electric water whatever you want to
concentrate you prepared finding
different ways and so if we're boiling
hydrogen off you know there's no purpose
to do that unless we're actually using
it and like I said this is what I'll
heat my shop with this year during this
during the winter we seal it together we
put everything putting everything to get